The Guide to the American Short Line Railroad Association records, 1912-1971
American Short Line Railroad Association records, 1912-1971
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
American Short Line Railroad Association records, 1912-1971.
2945
American Short Line Railroad Association.
44.3 cubic ft. Tape recording included.
Records, minutes, correspondence, transcripts, tape recording.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes association records, files, and transcripts of regional and board of directors meetings; procedural files; active member files; reports and financial data on cases before the Interstate Commerce Commission; non-member and inactive member files; and Association newsletter VIEWS AND NEWS, 1969-1971.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
A Short Line Railroad Association was first organized in 1910, and 22 railroads formed the Short Line Railroad Association of the Southeast in 1913. The group became a national association, serving 177 members by 1918. In 1920, the Western Association of Short Line Railroads affiliated with this Association. This is a non-profit, unincorporated association, whose actions are advisory only and nonbinding upon its members. Members are Class I and II line-haul, switching and terminal companies in 43 states.
The American Short Line Railroad Association, with stated objectives to "...provide cooperative action in the consideration and solutions of problems of management and policy affecting...short line railroads..." and "...to promote Federal legislation of benefit and resist the enactment of legislation that would be detrimental to the railroad industry," has deposited in the Cornell University Department of Manuscripts and University Archives records documenting the history of the association and its member roads, 1912-1967.
Formally organized in 1913, although a predecessor was formed in 1910, the first section of this listing is a record of the association itself, its internal operation and general reference and technical records. With the membership fluctuating as roads felt the need for cooperative action in the face of Federal legislation and for a statutory agent to represent them in Washington, as required by the provisions of the Interstate Commerce Act, service was provided to the varied interests of short line haul roads, switching and terminal companies and these records are divided into two sections, active and inactive and non-member roads.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records, minutes, correspondence, transcripts of meetings of the American Short Line Railroad Association. Includes association records, 1923-1965, which concern internal operations, files, and regional and board of directors meetings (includes one tape recording of the 1963 annual meeting); procedural files, 1912-1967, which cover topics such as classification, demurrage, freight rates, foreign tariffs, advertising, and railroad financing; active member files, 1913-1966, including correspondence, reports and financial data on cases before the Interstate Commerce Commission, for which the Association often acted as statutory agent and legal counsel for its members; and non- member and inactive member files, 1912-1964, including abandonments or compensation claims against the U.S. under provisions of the Transportation Act of 1920. Also includes Association newsletter VIEWS AND NEWS, 1969-1971.
SUBJECTS
Names:
American Short Line Railroad Association.; Interstate Commerce Commission.; Short Line Railroad Association of the Southeast.; Western Association of Short Line Railroads.
Titles:
Views and news.
Subjects:
Railroads--Commuting traffic.; Railroads (short lines.)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Association Records
Boxes 1-6
Series II. Procedural Files
Boxes 7-14
Series III. Active Member Files
Boxes 15-34
Series IV. Non- member and Inactive Member Files
Boxes 35-44
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Association Records, 1923, 191965.
  Concerns the internal operations of the Association: meetings of its board of directors and executive board, regional meetings of member railroads and annual meetings. Include agendas and minutes of meetings; correspondence between those attending and officers of the Association; notes, memos and correspondence on arrangements, speakers, entertainment and menus; stenographic transcripts of the proceedings of most annual meetings (1923-1962), special meetings (1929, 1932) and an executive board meeting (1933); and an original tape recording of the 1963 annual meeting.
  - Board of Directors Meeting, June 9, 1948, Washington, D.C.; June 2, 1948 to July 15, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Correspondence
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Feb. 17, 1949, Washington, D.C.; Jan. 4, 1949 to Feb. 17, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Agenda, recpts., reports, minutes
  - Board of Directors Meeting, June 22, 1949, Washington, D.C. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Minutes, reports, lists, agenda
    Association business
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Sept. 26, 1949, Chicago, Illinois; Aug. 18, 1949 to Sept. 26, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Reports, lists, minutes
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Jan. 24, 1950 Washington, D.C.; Dec. 13, 1949 to Jan. 24, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Minutes, list, correspondence
  - Board of Directors Meeting, June 29, 1950, Washington, D.C.; May 10, 1950 to July 20, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Correspondence, minutes, agenda, finaicial statement, lists
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Oct. 2/3, 1950, Tulsa, Oklahoma; Aug. 4, 1950 to Oct. 3, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Minutes, correspondence
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Feb. 13, 1951, Washington, D.C.; Dec. 29, 1950 to Feb. 13, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Minutes, reports, agenda, lists
  - Board of Directors Meeting, June 5, 1951, Washington, D.C.; Apr. 14, 1951 to June 6, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Minutes, correspondence, guest list, agenda
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Aug. 31, 1951, Washington, D.C. (token); Aug. 1, 1951 to Aug. 31, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Correspondence, minutes
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Oct. 3, 1951, New Orleans, Louisiana; Aug. 31, 1951 to Oct. 3, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Minutes, lists, resolution
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Feb. 19, 1952, Washington, D.C.; Nov. 19, 1951 to Aug. 29, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Correspondence, minutes, lists
  - Board of Directors Meeting, June 3, 1952, Chicago, Illinois; Apr. 25, 1942 to June 4, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Minutes, correspondence, lists, memo
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Oct. 2, 1952, San Francisco, California; Aug. 5, 1952 to Oct. 2, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Minutes, resolution, correspondence
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Feb. 19, 1953, Washington, D.C.; Nov. 24, 1952 to Mar. 10, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Correspondence, lists, minutes, agenda
  - Board of Directors Meeting, June 23, 1953, Atlantic City; June 5, 1953 to June 23, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Minutes, lists, memos, agenda, correspondence
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Dec. 8, 1953, Chicago; Sept. 10, 1953 to Dec. 15, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Correspondence, minutes, resolution, budget, lists, reports, agenda
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Apr. 13, 1954, Washington, D.C.; Jan. 7, 1954 to Apr. 16, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Aug. 19, 1954, Chicago; July 8, 1954 to Sept. 7, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Lists, correspondence, agenda
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Oct. 18, 1954, New York; Sept. 9, 1954 to Sept. 29, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Agenda, budget, resolutions, correspondence
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Apr. 11, 1955, Washington, D.C.; Dec. 31, 1954 to Apr. 21, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Minutes, correspondence, questionnaire
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Oct. 10, 1955, Chicago; Aug. 3, 1955 to Oct. 21, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Minutes, financial statement, agenda
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Jan. 19, 1956, Washington, D.C.; Dec. 16, 1955 to Feb. 23, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Correspondence, memos, minutes, list, agenda
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Apr. 17, 1956, Washington, D.C.; Feb. 21, 1956 to Apr. 23, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Minutes, agenda, correspondence
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Sept. 24/25, 1956, Denver; Aug. 7, 1956 to Oct. 2, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Minutes, financial statements, correspondence
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Jan. 30, 1957, Washington, D.C.; Nov. 16, 1956 to Feb. 5, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Lists, minutes, correspondence, agenda
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Apr. 15, 1957, Washington, D.C.; Jan. 31, 1957 to Feb. 5, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    List, correspondence
  - Board of Directors Meetings, Sept. 30-57 to 10, 191, 1957 Washington, D.C.; Aug. 22, 1957 to Oct. 9, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Minutes, financial statements, correspondence, news article, agenda, resolutions
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Apr. 14, 1958, Washington, D.C.; Jan. 16, 1958 to Apr. 16, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Minutes, financial statements, agenda, correspondence
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Sept. 29, 1958, Savannah, Georgia; Aug. 29, 1958 to Sept. 8, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Minutes, budget, agenda, resolutions
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Sept. 30, 1958, Savannah, Georgia; Aug. 8, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Minutes, financial report
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Dec. 30, 1958, Washington, D.C. (token); Dec. 1, 1958 to Dec. 30, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Feb. 4, 1959, Washington, D.C.; Dec. 23, 1958 to Feb. 26, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Minutes, reports, financial statements, lists, agenda, correspondence
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Apr. 9, 1959, Washington, D.C.; Mar. 2, 1959 to Apr. 16, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Sept. 22, 1959, Washington, D.C.; July 6, 1959 to Sept. 30, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Minutes, financial reports, correspondence
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Mar. 9, 1960, Washington, D.C. (token); Feb. 19, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Memo
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Apr. 18, 1960, Washington, D.C.; Feb. 17, 1960 to Apr. 30, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Report, minutes, list, agenda, correspondence
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Sept. 28, 1960, Washington, D.C. (token); Aug. 26, 1960 to Sept. 28, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Report
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Oct. 3/4, 1960, Green Bay, Wisconsin; June 7, 1960 to Dec. 7, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Correspondence, minutes, agenda, reports, resolutions
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Oct. 3/4, 1960, Green Bay, Wisconsin; June 7, 1960 to Apr. 5, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Correspondence, minutes, reports, lists
    Finances, Eastern Region, federal legislation, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, public policy problems in transportation
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Feb. 28, 1961, Washington, D.C. (token); Feb. 8, 1961 to Feb. 28, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Apr. 11, 1961, Washington, D.C.; Mar. 9, 1961 to Apr. 21, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Oct. 30/31, 1961, San Francisco, California; Sept. 29, 1961 to Oct. 19, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Correspondence, agenda, financial statements, resolutions, list
    Finances, budget, dues, salaries and expenses of officers
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Oct. 30/31, 1961, San Francisco, California; Apr. 21, 1961 to Oct. 19, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    Correspondence, agenda, financial statements, resolutions, lists, minutes
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Feb. 28, 1962, Washington, D.C. (token); Feb. 14, 1962 to Feb. 28, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Apr. 9, 1962, Washington, D.C.; Jan. 24, 1962 to Apr. 9, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    Minutes, lists, agenda, financial statements
  - Executive Committee Meeting, Apr. 25, 1962 Washington, D.C.; Apr. 9, 1962 to May 1, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    Minutes, correspondence, financial statements
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Oct. 1/2, 1962, Dallas, Texas; July 25, 1962 to Nov. 7, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Minutes, resolutions, financial statements, correspondence, memos, lists
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Apr. 8, 1963, Washington, D.C.; Jan. 28, 1963 to Apr. 26, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    Minutes, correspondence, agenda
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Sept. 30, 1963 to Oct. 1, 1963, Edgewater Park, Mississippi; Sept. 20, 1963 to Nov. 1, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Sept. 30, 1963 to Oct. 1, 1963, Edgewater Park, Mississippi; Oct. 9, 1962 to Sept. 20, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    Agenda, resolutions, minutes, financial statements, list
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Apr. 13, 1964, Washington, D.C.; Dec. 12, 1963 to Mar. 9, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    Agenda, correspondence, minutes
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Apr. 13, 1964, Washington, D.C.; Mar. 12, 1964 to Mar. 31, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    List, agenda, minutes, reports
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Apr. 13, 1964, Washington, D.C.; Sept. 30, 1963 to Mar. 31, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    Minutes, financial statements, lists, reports, questionnaire
    Finances, Interstate Commerce Commission proceedings, proposed amendment to the Interstate Commerce Act and the Federal Aviation Act of 1958
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Apr. 11, 1965, Washington, D.C.; Oct. 26, 1964 to May 10, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    Minutes, reports, lists, correspondence, agenda
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Sept. 27/28, 1965, Milwaukee, Wisconsin; Sept. 15, 1965 to Oct. 25, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    Correspondence, minutes, agenda, resolutions
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Sept. 27/28, 1965, Milwaukee, Wisconsin; Mar. 10, 1965 to Sept. 29, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    Agenda, resolutions, minutes, reports
    Association Constitution amendment, railroad mergers, Harry Randall Malaby, John Stephen Babbitt
  - "1950-Eastern Region-Buffalo-5-9-50"; Mar. 15, 1950 to May 10, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Report, lists, questionnaires, correspondence
  - "1951-Eastern Reg.-New York-4-12-51"; Nov. 14, 1950 to May 8, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, list, minutes
  - "1952-Eastern Reg.-Buffalo-5-15-52"; Mar. 20, 1952 to May 22, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, lists, minutes, speeches, notes
  - "1952-Western Reg.-Green Bay-5-22-52"; Apr. 15, 1952 to July 11, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Minutes, records, correspondence, speeches, clippings, agenda
    Correspondants: C.A. Miller, v.p., gen. counsel, Shortline Assoc.
  - "You and the Railroads"-speech for Western Regional Meeting; May 22, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    James Milton Hood, pres., Shortline Assoc.
  - "1952-Pacific Reg.-Salt Lake City-4-9-52"; Feb. 28, 1951 to Apr. 10, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Correspondence, minutes, lists, agenda
    Correspondants: Julian M. Bamberger, v.p., Pacific region, Shortline Assoc.
  - "1953-Eastern Reg.-Buffalo-3-25-53"; Oct. 14, 1952 to Apr. 14, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Correspondence, minutes, agenda, schedule
  - "1953-Southern Reg.-Atlanta-4-2-53"; Oct. 14, 1952 to Apr. 17, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Correspondence, agenda, financial report
  - "1953-Western Reg.-Des Moines-4-8-53"; Oct. 14, 1952 to May 6, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Minutes, list, clippings, agenda, correspondence
  - "1953-Southwestern Reg.-Dallas-4-6-53"; Oct. 14, 1952 to May 6, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Minutes, lists, correspondence, itinerary
  - "1953-Pacific Reg.-Portland, Oregon-4-20-53"; Oct. 9, 1952 to May 18, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    List, minutes, agenda, correspondence, itinerary
  - "1954-Eastern Reg.-Boston-5-19-54"; Mar. 26, 1954 to June 1, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Correspondence, lists, brochure, report
  - "1954-Southern Reg.-Savannah-4-20-54"; Dec. 22, 1953 to Mar. 20, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - "1954-Western Reg.-Green Bay-4-29-54"; Jan. 26, 1954 to May 17, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Correspondence, report
  - "1954-Southwestern Reg.-St. Louis-4-27-54"; Jan. 25, 1954 to Apr. 27, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Minutes, correspondence, lists
  - "1954-Pacific Reg.-Reno, Nevada-5-4-54"; Jan. 27, 1953 to May 4, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Minutes, correspondence, brochure, lists
  - "1955-Eastern Reg.-Buffalo-5-18-55"; Jan. 21, 1955 to May 18, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - "1955-Southern Reg.-Atlanta-4-20-55"; Jan. 21, 1955 to Sept. 5, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - "1955-Western Reg.-Escanaba, Mich.-5-26-55"; Jan. 21, 1955 to June 23, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Speeches, minutes
  - "1955-Southwestern Reg.-New Orleans-4-15-55"; Jan. 10, 1955 to Apr. 22, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Minutes, speeches, news clippings, correspondence, brochures
  - "1955-Pacific Reg.-Phoenix-4-15-55"; Nov. 15, 1954 to May 10, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - "1956-Eastern Reg.-Pittsburgh-3-21-56"; Jan. 27, 1956 to July 2, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - "1956-Southern Reg.-New Orleans-2-23-56"; Jan. 12, 1956 to Oct. 25, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Correspondence, minutes, agenda
  - "1956-Southern Reg.-Charlotte-7-25-56"; July 6, 1956 to July 25, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Speech, minutes, agenda, correspondence
  - "1956-Western Reg.-Cedar Rapids, Iowa-5-2-56"; Apr. 6, 1956 to May 2, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - "1956-Pacific Reg.-Carmel, California-5-11-56"; Nov. 19, 1955 to May 11, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - "1957-Eastern Reg.-Pittsburgh-6-30-57"; Mar. 13, 1957 to May 23, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Reports, correspondence, legislative bills, agenda
  - "1957-Western Reg.-Minneapolis-5-23-57"; Feb. 13, 1957 to June 3, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Minutes, report, speech, agenda, correspondence
  - "1957-Pacific Reg.-Salt Lake City-5-16-57"; Feb. 12, 1957 to June 3, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - "1957-Southern Reg.-Atlanta-6-19-57"; Mar. 7, 1957 to June 20, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Agenda, minutes, correspondence
  - 1958 -Western Reg. Meeting; Apr. 4, 1958 to June 19, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Minutes, correspondence, program, clippings
  - 1958 -Southern Reg. Meeting; Dec. 23, 1957 to May 7, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Correspondence, speech, minutes, list
    Correspondents: Thomas Healy, member, U.S. Railroad Retirement Bd.
  - 1958 -Southwestern Reg. Meeting; Nov. 7, 1957 to May 13, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Correspondence, minutes, clippings, list, agenda
  - 1958 -Pacific Reg. Meeting; Dec. 9, 1957 to May 14, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Minutes, list, agenda, correspondence, brochure
  - 1958 -Eastern Reg. Meeting; Dec. 3, 1957 to May 21, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    Minutes, speech, list, correspondence
    Correspondents: J.A. Sherman, Eastern rep., Claims Research Bureau, Assoc. Am. Railroads
  - "1959-Eastern Reg. Meeting"; Aug. 4, 1958 to May 20, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - "1959-Pacific Reg. Meeting"; Dec. 16, 1957 to June 19, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - "1959-Southwestern Reg. Meeting"; Oct. 16, 1958 to June 9, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    Minutes, list, correspondence, agenda
  - "1959-Western Reg. Meeting"; Feb. 26, 1959 to Aug. 12, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - "1960-Eastern Reg. Meeting"; May 6, 1960 to June 22, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - "1960-Western Reg. Meeting"; Jan. 25, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - "1960-Southwestern Reg. Meeting"; Oct. 21, 1959 to May 18, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    Minutes, list, correspondence, brochure, news clippings, program
  - "1960-Southern Reg. Meeting"; Jan. 26, 1960 to July 21, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    Correspondence, agenda, minutes
  - "1960-Pacific Reg. Meeting"; Nov. 16, 1959 to Sept. 27, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    Correspondence, minutes, itinerary, list, agenda
  - "1961-Eastern Reg. Meeting"; Apr. 24, 1961 to May 31, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    Correspondence, list
  - "1961-Pacific Reg. Meeting"; June 21, 1960 to May 30, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - "1961-Southwestern Reg. Meeting, also see Western Reg. Meeting"; May 9, 1961 to June 1, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    Correspondence, agenda
  - "1961-Western Reg. Meeting"; June 15, 1961 to June 19, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - "1961-Southern Reg. Meeting"; Feb. 6, 1961 to May 10, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    C. speech, correspondence
  - 1962 -"Pacific Reg. Meeting"; Sept. 8, 1960 to June 14, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    Questionnaire, correspondence, registration, pictures, minutes, program, reports
    Meeting arrangements, Shortline Traffic office (Pacific region), pictures not identified
  - 1962 -"Eastern Reg. Meeting"; Jan. 23, 1962 to June 13, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - 1962 -"Western Reg. Meeting"; Jan. 17, 1962 to Oct. 2, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - 1962 -"Southwestern Reg. Meeting"; Nov. 9, 1961 to Feb. 16, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    Proceedings, list, correspondence
  - 1962 -"Southern Reg. Meeting"; Jan. 11, 1962 to May 11, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    Correspondence, minutes, list
  - 1963 -"Western"; May 9, 1963 to June 20, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    Correspondence, clippings, program
  - 1963 -"Eastern"; Apr. 25, 1963 to May 27, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    Correspondence, minutes, lists, speech
  - 1963 -"Southern"; Feb. 20, 1963 to May 29, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - 1963 -"Southwestern"; Oct. 4, 1962 to Apr. 24, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - 1963 -"Pacific"; Nov. 20, 1962 to Oct. 10, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    List, minutes, correspondence, itinerary, brochures
  - 1964 -Eastern Reg; Jan. 13, 1964 to May 28, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - 1964 -Southern Reg; Jan. 24, 1964 to June 24, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    List, minutes, correspondence
  - 1964 -Western Reg; Mar. 24, 1964 to July 8/9, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - 1964 -Southwestern Reg; Nov. 1, 1963 to July 7, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - 1964 -Pacific Reg; Nov. 26, 1963 to June 25, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    Correspondence, minutes, itinerary, program
  - 1948 Annual Meeting, Oct. 12, 1948, Chicago"; Mar. 25, 1948 to Oct. 23, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Minutes, article, correspondence, report
  - "Annual, 9-26-49, Chicago: 1949 Annual Meeting"; Feb. 22, 1949 to Oct. 11, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, lists, minutes
  - "Annual, 9-26-49, Chicago: Agenda - 1949"; July 1, 1949 to Aug. 16, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Correspondence, reports
  - "Annual, 9-26-49, Chicago: Annual 1949 Proceedings"; June 6, 1949 to June 11, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - "Annual, 10-3-50, Tulsa: 1950 Annual Meeting"; Oct. 21, 1949 to Oct. 31, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, clippings, memos, agenda
  - "Annual, 10-3-50, Tulsa: Scrapbook folder"; Oct. 2/5, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Tickets, invitations, schedules, menus, clippings
  - "Annual, 10-3-50, Tulsa: Annual 1950 - Agenda"; 1950 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Pamphlet
  - "Annual, 10-3-50, Tulsa: Annual 1950 - Proceedings"; July 12, 1950 to Aug. 2, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - "Annual, 10-3-51, New Orleans: 1951 Annual Meeting"; Nov. 27, 1950 to Oct. 10, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Correspondence, proclamation, pictures
  - "Annual, 10-3-51, New Orleans: Scott Wilson and Associates H-3271"; Aug. 6, 1951 to Feb. 5, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Photographs, blueprints, correspondence, news clippings
  - Agenda - 38th Annual Meeting, Am. Short Line Railroad Assoc; Oct. 3/4, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Agenda, reports, American Short Line Railroad Assoc. constitution
  - "Annual 1951 - Proceedings"; July 11, 1951 to Oct. 9, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - "Annual, 10-2-52, San Francisco"; Oct. 16, 1951 to Oct. 4, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Lists, minutes, correspondence, report, schedule
  - "Annual, 10-2-52, San Francisco: Annual 1952 - Agenda"; July 15, 1952 to Sept. 18, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - "Annual, 10-2-52, San Francisco: Annual 1952 - Proceedings"; Mar. 14, 1952 to Jan. 8, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - 1953 Annual Meeting, Atlantic City, June 23, 1953; Sept. 27, 1952 to June 26, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - 1953 Annual Meeting, Atlantic City, June 23, 1953; June 23, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Agenda
  - "1954 Annual Meeting, New York, 10-19-54"; Dec. 11, 1953 to Nov. 29, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Correspondence, lists